[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these was supposedly built to house 8 human hairs?", "correct_answer": "The Shwedagon Pagoda", "incorrect_answers": ["The Torii Pagoda", "The Masudi Temple", "The Chenwuku Temple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country is the only member of the European Union that is partly located in Africa?", "correct_answer": "Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "UK", "Malta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tinctures in herbal medicine are made by mixing dried herbs with oils, such as sesame oil or almond oil.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Warren Commission, was established on November 29, 1963 by Lyndon B. Johnson to investigate what?", "correct_answer": "The assassination of John F. Kennedy", "incorrect_answers": ["The war crimes in Vietnam", "The shooting at Kensington University", "The Watergate Scandal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of which beautiful flower also refers to an e-mail server/client?", "correct_answer": "Lotus", "incorrect_answers": ["Orchid", "Rose", "Lily"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The female of this species is sometimes called a Blue Flyer, because of its bluish coloration.", "correct_answer": "red kangaroo", "incorrect_answers": ["white heron", "emu", "kookaburra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mary Kay Place, who played Melanies mother Pearl in Sweet Home Alabama, has also starred on Greys Anatomy with Patrick Dempsey, who played Melanies fiance Andrew.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Portuguese explorer was the first to sight the island of Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "Diego Dias", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry the Navigator", "Diogo Cao", "Vasco da Gama"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the 1990 US census the most common surname is Smith. What is the second most common name?", "correct_answer": "Johnson", "incorrect_answers": ["Brown", "Williams", "Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Salmon is high in which of these?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["protein", "omega-3 fatty acids", "vitamin D"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the first African-American to produce and direct a full-length feature film.", "correct_answer": "Oscar Micheaux", "incorrect_answers": ["Gordon Parks", "Paul Greengrass", "Keith Gordon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the usual color of the gooseberry fruit?", "correct_answer": "Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Purple", "Orange", "Red"]}]